Finding Aid for Provost and Executive Vice-President for Academic Affairs (University of Michigan) Central Files
Bentley Historical Library
- Central Files
  - 1990-1991
    - Schools and Colleges Files
      - Non-budget
        - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of
          - Departments
            - General (Box 291)
              - Appointments, Promotions and Recruitment (Box 316)
              - Complaints and Grievances (student) (Box 316)
            - Biology (Box 291)
            - Chemistry (Box 291)
            - Classical Studies (Box 291)
            - Communications (Box 291)
            - Economics (Box 291)
            - English (Box 291)
            - Geological Sciences (Box 291)
            - Germanic Languages and Literature (Box 291)
            - History (Box 291)
            - History of Art (Box 291)
            - Judaic Studies (Box 291)
            - Linguistics (Box 291)
            - Mathematics (Box 291)
            - Near Eastern Studies (Box 291)
            - Philosophy (Box 291)
            - Physics (Box 291)
            - Political Science (Box 291)
            - Psychology (Box 291)
            - Romance Languages (Box 291)
            - Slavic Languages and Literature (Box 291)
            - Sociology
              - General (Box 291)
              - SOC 102: Sociology of Love (discontinuance of) (Box 291)
        - Medical School
          - General (Box 291)
          - Appointments, Promotions and Recruitment, 4 folders (Box 316)
          - Biomedical Research (Box 291)
          - Biophysics Research Division
            - General (Box 291)
            - Appointments and Recruitment (Box 316)
          - Briefing Materials (for meetings with Provost) (Box 291)
          - Clinical Track Faculty (Box 291)
          - Complaints and Grievances
            - Faculty/Staff (Box 316)
            - Students (Box 316)
          - Dean Search (Box 316)
          - Inteflex Program Information Packet (Box 291)
          - Regent's Communications (Box 291)
          - Unit for Laboratory Animal Medicine (Box 291)
        - Music, School of
          - General (Box 292)
          - Appointments, Promotions and Recruitment (Box 316)
          - Complaints (Box 316)
        - Natural Resources, School of
          - General, 2 folders (Box 292)
          - Appointments, Promotions and Recruitment (Box 316)
          - Dean Search (Box 316)
        - Nursing, School of
          - General (Box 292)
          - Appointments, Promotions and Recruitment (Box 316)
        - Pharmacy, College of (Box 292)
        - Public Health, School of
          - General (Box 292)
          - Appointments, Promotions and Recruitment (Box 316)
          - Social Work, School of (Box 316)
          - General (Box 292)
          - Appointments, Promotions and Recruitment (Box 316)
      - Budget Conferences (Box 292)
        - General Information (Box 292)
        - Summaries (Box 292)
        - Academic Affairs (Box 292)
        - Academic Planning and Analysis, Office of (Box 292)
        - Admissions (Box 292)
        - Affirmative Action (Box 292)
        - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of (Box 292)
        - Art, School of (Box 292)
        - Business Administration, School of (Box 292)
        - Business and Finance, Vice President for (Box 292)
        - Centers
          - Education of Women (Box 292)
          - Human Growth and Development (Box 292)
          - Research on Learning and Teaching (Box 292)
        - Communications, Vice President for (Box 292)
        - Communicative Disorders Clinic (Box 292)
        - Dentistry, School of (Box 292)
        - Development, Vice President for (Box 292)
        - Developmental and Reproductive Biology (Box 292)
        - Education, School of (Box 292)
        - Engineering, College of (Box 292)
        - Extension Service (Box 292)
        - Financial Aid (Box 292)
        - Government Relations, Vice President for (Box 292)
        - Information and Library Studies, School of (Box 292)
        - Information Technology Division (Box 292)
        - Institutes
          - Gerontology (Box 292)
          - Labor and Industrial Relations (Box 292)
          - Public Policy Studies (Box 292)
        - Law School (Box 292)
        - Libraries
          - Bentley Historical Library (Box 293)
          - Clements Library (Box 293)
          - University Library (Box 293)
        - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of (Box 293)
        - Medical School (Box 293)
        - Minority Affairs (Box 293)
        - Museum of Art (Box 293)
        - Music, School of (Box 293)
        - Natural Resources, School of (Box 293)
        - Nursing, School of (Box 293)
        - Opportunity Program (Box 293)
        - Orientation (Box 293)
        - Pharmacy, College of (Box 293)
        - Physical Education, Division of (Box 293)
        - President, Office of (Box 293)
        - Public Health, School of (Box 293)
        - Rackham School of Graduate Studies (Box 293)
        - Recreational Sports (Box 293)
        - Registrar (Box 293)
        - Research, Vice President for (Box 293)
        - SACUA (Box 293)
        - Scheduling (Box 293)
        - Social Work, School of (Box 293)
        - Student Services, Vice President for (Box 293)
    - Chronological Files
      - 1990
        - July-September, 3 folders (Box 293)
        - October-December, 3 folders (Box 294)
      - 1991
        - January-June, 6 folders (Box 294)
  - 1991-1992
    - Alphabetical Files (Box 320)
      - Academic Affairs Advisory Council (AAAC) (Box 320)
      - Academic Affairs Office (Box 320)
      - Academic Planning and Analysis (OAPA) (Box 320)
      - Academic Program Group (APG) (Box 320)
      - Academic Services Board (ASB) (Box 320)
      - Academic Service Units (Box 320)
      - Accreditation (Box 320)
      - Admissions, General (Box 320)
      - Advisory Committee on University Budgets (ACUB) (Box 320)
      - Affirmative Action Office (Box 320)
      - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) (Box 320)
      - Association of American Universities (AAU) (Box 320)
      - Athletics (Box 320)
      - Audits
        - Special Investigation Reports (Box 317)
          [Personnel records restricted until January 1, 2022 ]
      - Awards (Box 320)
        - General (Box 320)
        - Michigan Association of Governing Boards (MAGB) (Box 320)
        - Faculty Nominations (Box 317)
      - Budget (Box 320)
        - General, 1991/92 (Box 320)
        - General, 1992/93 (Box 320)
      - Budget Priorities Committee (Box 320)
      - Budget Reallocation (Box 320)
      - State Budget Requests, 1992/93 (Box 320)
      - Business and Industry (Box 320)
      - Business Roundtable (Box 320)
      - Calendar, University (Box 321)
      - Campaign Operations Group (Box 321)
      - Campaign Steering Executive Committee (Box 321)
      - Capital campaign (Box 321)
      - Capital Funds Commitment Forms (Box 321)
      - Centers
        - General (Box 321)
        - Chinese Studies (Box 321)
        - Continuing Education for Women (CEW) (Box 321)
        - Human Growth and Development (CHGD) (Box 321)
        - Macromolecular Research (Box 321)
        - Population Studies (Box 321)
        - Research on Learning and Teaching (CRLT) (Box 321)
      - Committees
        - Committee on Budget Administration (CBA) (Box 321)
        - Committee on the Economic Status of the Faculty (CESF) (Box 321)
        - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (CIC), 2 folders (Box 321)
      - Communication (Future Governance of Student Publications) (Box 321)
      - Community Relations (Box 321)
      - Comprehensive Studies Program (CSP) (Box 321)
      - Computers (Box 321)
      - Computerized Academic Record (Box 321)
      - Consortium for International Earth Science Information Network (CIESIN) (Box 321)
      - Detroit Rackham Building (Box 321)
      - Development (includes APG Subcommittee), 2 folders (Box 321)
      - Disability (Box 321)
      - Discrimination (Box 321)
      - Diversity (Box 321)
      - Division of Research Development and Administration (DRDA) (Box 321)
      - Economic Forecasting Group (Box 322)
      - Enrollment (Box 322)
      - Environment (Box 322)
      - Executive Committee (Box 322)
      - Executive Computing Committee (Box 322)
      - Faculty (Box 322)
      - Federal Relations (Box 322)
      - Finance (Vice President and Chief Financial Officer), 2 folders (Box 322)
      - Financial Aid, Office of (Box 322)
      - Financial Reports (Box 322)
      - Foundation Fundraising Committee (Box 322)
      - Foundations
        - General (Box 322)
        - Cook (Box 322)
        - Hewlett (Box 322)
        - Kellogg (Box 322)
        - Kresge (Box 322)
        - McKinley (Box 322)
        - Mellon (Box 322)
        - Skillman (Box 322)
      - Futures Group (Box 322)
      - Gateway Campus (Box 323)
      - General Counsel
        - General (Box 323)
        - Communication (Box 317)
        - Indemnification (Box 323)
      - Gifts, Endowments, etc (Box 323)
      - Giving Campaign (Box 323)
      - Global Change (Box 323)
      - Government
        - Federal (Box 323)
        - State (Box 323)
      - Government Relations (Box 323)
      - Graduate Student Assistants (Box 323)
      - Grievances (faculty/staff) (Box 317)
        [Personnel records restricted until July 01, 2022 ]
      - Handicapped (Box 323)
      - Harassment Policy (Box 323)
      - Higher Education (Box 323)
      - Honorary Degrees (Box 323)
      - Housing (Box 323)
      - Human Resources Review Committee (Box 323)
      - Indirect Cost, 2 folders (Box 323)
      - Information Technology (Box 324)
      - Institutes
        - Gerontology (IOG) (Box 324)
        - Humanities (Box 324)
        - Industrial Technology (ITI) (Box 324)
        - Labor and Industrial Relations (ILIR) (Box 324)
        - Public Policy Studies (IPPS) (Box 324)
        - Social Research (ISR) (Box 324)
      - Intellectual Properties (Box 324)
      - International Affairs
        - General, 2 folders (Box 324)
        - University Council for International Academic Affairs (UCIAA) (Box 324)
      - Journalism (Box 324)
      - K-12/UM Collaboration (Box 324)
      - Libraries
        - General (Box 324)
        - Bentley (Box 324)
        - Ford (Box 324)
        - University (Box 324)
      - Management Committee (Box 324)
      - Medical Affairs, Vice Provost for (Box 324)
      - Medical Center (Box 324)
      - Michigan (State of) (Box 324)
      - Michigan Education Trust (MET) (Box 324)
      - Michigan Information Technology Network (MITN) (Box 324)
      - Michigan Mandate (Box 324)
      - Michigan Partnership for New Education (Box 324)
      - Michigan Society of Fellows (Box 324)
      - Middle English Dictionary (Box 324)
      - Minorities
        - General (Box 325)
        - Commission on Minority Student Recruitment and Graduation (Box 325)
        - Enrollment (Box 325)
        - Faculty (Box 325)
        - King/Chavez/Parks Program (Box 325)
        - Martin Luther King Jr. Day (Box 325)
        - Racism (Box 325)
      - Minority Affairs, Office of (Box 325)
      - Multicultural University, Council on a (Box 325)
      - Museums (UM)
        - General (Box 325)
        - Art (Box 325)
        - Kelsey (Box 325)
      - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges (NASULGC) (Box 325)
      - National Science Board (Box 325)
      - National Science Foundation (NSF) (Box 325)
      - Neurosciences Program
        - General (Box 325)
      - News and Information Services (Box 325)
      - North Campus (Box 325)
      - Parking (Box 325)
      - Peer Institutions (Box 325)
      - Personnel
        - General (Box 325)
        - Dual Careers (Box 325)
        - Faculty (Box 325)
      - Plant Extension (Box 325)
      - Police (University of Michigan) (Box 325)
      - Police Oversight Committee (Box 325)
      - Politically Correct (Box 325)
      - President's Advisory Commission on Minority Affairs (PACMA) (Box 325)
      - President's Advisory Committee on Women's Issues (PACWI) (Box 325)
      - President's Council (UM) (Box 325)
      - Presidents' Council of the State Universities of Michigan (Box 325)
      - President's Office (Box 325)
      - Promotions
        - General (Box 325)
        - Recommendations (Box 317)
      - Provost's Administrative Group (PAG) (Box 326)
      - Provost's Advisory Committee on Excellence (PACE) (Box 326)
      - Public Service (Box 326)
      - Publications (Box 326)
      - Regents
        - General (Box 326)
        - Communications, 2 folders (Box 326)
      - Registrar's Office (Box 326)
      - Requests (Navy V-12 Program during World War II) (Box 326)
      - Research
        - General (Box 326)
        - Research Advisory Group (Box 326)
        - Vice President (Box 326)
      - Reserve Officer Training Corps (ROTC) (Box 326)
      - Residency (Box 326)
      - Retirement, Mandatory (Box 326)
      - Safety and Security Advisory Committee (Box 326)
      - Salary
        - General (Box 326)
        - Salary Equity Study (Box 326)
      - Scholarships and Fellowships (Box 326)
      - Searches (Expenditures) (Box 326)
      - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA) (Box 326)
      - Senate Assembly (Box 326)
      - Sexual Orientation (Box 326)
      - SHARE (Special Hiring and Recruitment Effort for Senior faculty Women) (Box 327)
      - Space (Box 327)
      - Staff Benefits (Box 327)
      - Students
        - General (Box 327)
        - Health Insurance (Box 327)
      - Student Services, Vice President for (Box 327)
      - Substance Abuse (Box 327)
      - Surveys (Box 327)
      - Target of Opportunity (TOO)
        - General (Box 327)
      - Tenure (Box 327)
      - Total Quality (Box 327)
      - Travel and Hosting Policy (Box 327)
      - Tuition and Fees (Box 327)
      - Undergraduate Education (Box 327)
      - Undergraduate Initiatives (Box 327)
      - United Way (Box 327)
      - University Events
        - General (Box 327)
        - 175th Anniversary (Box 327)
      - University of Michigan (General Information) (Box 327)
      - University Press (Box 327)
      - University Relations (Box 327)
      - Women (Box 327)
        (see also President's Advisory Commission on Women's Issues)
    - Schools and Colleges Files
      - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of
        - General (Box 328)
        - Appointments, Promotions and Recruitment (Box 317)
      - Art, School of (Box 328)
      - Business Administration, School of
        - General (Box 328)
        - Appointments, Promotions, and Recruitment (Box 317)
        - Davidson Institute (Box 328)
      - Dearborn Campus
        - General (Box 328)
        - Appointments, Promotions and Recruitment (Box 317)
      - Dentistry, School of
        - General (Box 328)
        - Appointments, Promotions and Recruitment (Box 317)
      - Education, School of
        - General (Box 328)
        - Appointments, Promotions and Recruitment (Box 317)
      - Engineering, College of
        - General (Box 328)
        - Appointments, Promotions and Recruitment (Box 317)
        - Lurie Donations (Box 317)
      - Flint Campus
        - General (Box 320)
        - Appointments, Promotions and Recruitment, 2 folders (Box 317)
      - Graduate Studies, Rackham School of (Box 328)
      - Information and Library Studies, School of
        - Appointments, Promotions and Recruitment (Box 317)
      - Kinesiology, Division of (formerly Division of Physical Education) (Box 328)
      - Law School (Box 328)
      - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of
        - General (Box 328)
        - Appointments, Promotions and Recruitment, 4 folders (Box 317)
        - Departments (Box 328)
          - Miscellaneous Departments (Box 328)
          - Anthropology (Box 328)
          - Chemistry (Box 328)
          - Classical Studies (Box 328)
          - Economics (Box 328)
          - English (Box 328)
          - Geological Sciences (Box 328)
          - History (Box 328)
          - Linguistics (Box 328)
          - Mathematics (Box 328)
          - Near Eastern Studies (Box 328)
          - Physics (Box 328)
          - Political Science (Box 328)
          - Psychology (Box 328)
      - Medical School
        - General (Box 328)
        - Appointments, Promotions and Recruitment, 3 folders (Box 317)
        - Inteflex (Box 328)
        - Regents' Communications (Box 328)
    - Schools and Colleges Files
      - Music, School of
        - General (Box 328)
        - Appointments, Promotions and Recruitment (Box 317)
      - Natural Resources, School of (Box 328)
      - Nursing, School of (Box 328)
      - Pharmacy, College of
        - Appointments, Promotions and Recruitment (Box 317)
      - Public Health, School of (Box 328)
        - General (Box 328)
        - Appointments, Promotions and Recruitment (Box 317)
      - Social Work, School of
        - General (Box 328)
        - Appointments, Promotions and Recruitment (Box 317)
    - Chronological Files
      - 1991
        - July-December, 6 folders (Box 329)
      - 1992
        - January-December, 12 folders (Box 329)
      - 1993
        - January-June, 6 folders (Box 329)
  - 1992-1993
    - Alphabetical Files
      - Academic Affairs Advisory Council (AAAC) (Box 330)
      - Academic Affairs Committee (Box 330)
      - Academic Affairs Office (Box 330)
      - Academic Planning and Analysis (OAPA) (Box 330)
      - Academic Program Group (APG), 2 folders
        - APG Development Subcommittee (Box 330)
      - Academic Services Board (ASB) (Box 330)
      - Admissions, General (Box 330)
      - Advisory Committee on University Budgets (ACUB) (Box 330)
      - Alumni (Box 330)
      - Articles (Box 330)
      - Arts, Vice Provost for the (Paul Boylan) (Box 330)
      - Association of American Universities (AAU) (Box 330)
      - Athletics (Box 330)
      - Audits (Box 318)
        [Personnel records restricted until July 01, 2023 ]
      - Awards
        - General (Box 330)
        - Henry Russel Award (Box 330)
      - Budget
        - General, 1992/93 (Box 330)
        - Capital Outlay (Box 330)
        - State Budget Requests
          - 1992/93 (Box 330)
          - 1993/94 (Box 330)
      - Business and Industry (Box 330)
      - Business Roundtable (Box 330)
      - Calendar, University (Box 330)
      - Campaign Operations Group (Box 330)
      - Campaign Steering Executive Committee (Box 330)
      - Capital Funds Commitment Forms (Box 330)
      - Centers
        - General (Box 330)
        - Chinese Studies (Box 330)
        - Continuing Education for Women (CEW) (Box 330)
        - Human Growth and Development (CHGD) (Box 330)
        - Macromolecular Research (Box 330)
        - Research on Learning and Teaching (CRLT) (Box 330)
        - Child Care (Box 330)
      - Commencement (Box 330)
      - Committees
        - Committee on Budget Administration (CBA 2 X 4) (Box 330)
        - Committee on the Economic Status of the Faculty (CESF) (Box 330)
        - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (CIC), 2 folders (Box 331)
      - Community Relations (Box 331)
      - Consortium for International Earth Science Information Network (CIESIN) (Box 331)
      - Detroit Observatory (Box 331)
      - Detroit Rackham Building (Box 331)
      - Development (Box 331)
      - Disability (Box 331)
      - Discrimination (Box 331)
      - Diversity (Box 331)
      - Division of Research Development and Administration (DRDA) (Box 331)
      - Dual Careers (Box 331)
      - Economic Forecasting Group (Box 331)
      - Enrollment (Box 331)
      - Environment (Box 331)
      - Evaluations (Box 331)
      - Executive Committee (Box 331)
      - Executive Computing Committee (Box 331)
      - Extension Service (Box 331)
      - Faculty (Box 331)
      - Federal Relations (Box 331)
      - Finance (Vice President and Chief Financial Officer) (Box 331)
      - Financial Aid (Box 331)
      - Financial Reports (Box 331)
      - Foundation Fundraising Committee (Box 331)
      - Foundations
        - General (Box 331)
        - Hewlett (Box 331)
        - Kellogg (Box 331)
        - Kresge (Box 331)
        - McKinley (Box 331)
        - Gateway Campus (Box 331)
      - General Counsel
        - General (Box 332)
        - Communications (Box 318)
          [Patient/client records restricted until July 1, 2103 ]
        - Indemnification (Box 332)
      - Gifts, Endowments, etc (Box 332)
      - Global Change (Box 332)
      - Government
        - Federal (Box 332)
        - State (Box 332)
      - Government Relations (Box 332)
      - Graduate Student Assistants/Graduate Employees Organization (GEO) (Box 332)
      - Handicapped (Box 332)
      - Harassment Policy (Box 332)
      - Higher Education (Box 332)
      - Honorary Degrees, 2 folders (Box 332)
      - Housing (Box 332)
      - Human Resources Review Committee (Box 332)
      - Indirect Cost (Box 332)
      - Information Technology Division (ITD), 4 folders (Box 318)
      - Information Technology Policy Committee (Box 318)
      - Institutes
        - General (Box 332)
        - Continuing Legal Education (ICLE) (Box 318)
        - Humanities (Box 332)
        - Industrial Technology (ITI) (Box 332)
        - Labor and Industrial Relations (ILIR) (Box 318)
        - Public Policy Studies (IPPS) (Box 332)
        - Social Research (ISR) (Box 332)
      - Intellectual Properties (Box 332)
      - Internal Revenue Service (IRS) Audit (Box 318)
      - International Affairs
        - General (Box 332)
        - University Council for International Academic Affairs (UCIAA) (Box 332)
      - Investments (Box 333)
      - K-12/UM Collaboration (Box 333)
      - Libraries
        - General (Box 333)
        - Bentley (Box 333)
        - Clements (Box 333)
        - Ford (Box 333)
        - University
          - Dean of Libraries (Box 333)
      - Manufacturing Initiative, Michigan Joint (Box 333)
      - Medical Affairs, Vice Provost for (Box 333)
      - Medical Center (Box 333)
      - Memberships (Box 333)
      - Michigan Education Trust (MET) (Box 333)
      - Michigan Information Technology Network (MITN) (Box 333)
      - Michigan Mandate (Box 333)
      - Michigan Society of Fellows (Box 333)
      - Michigan Student Assembly (MSA) (Box 333)
      - Middle English Dictionary (Box 318)
      - Minorities (Box 333)
        - General (Box 333)
        - Faculty (Box 333)
        - Martin Luther King Jr. Day (Box 333)
      - Minority Affairs, Office of
        - General (Box 333)
        - Minority Affairs Advisory Council (Box 333)
      - Multicultural University, Council on a (Box 333)
      - Museums (UM)
        - General (Box 333)
        - Art (Box 333)
      - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges (NASULGC) (Box 333)
      - National Science Foundation (NSF) (Box 333)
      - Neurosciences Program (Box 333)
      - New Pay Committee (Box 333)
      - News and Information Services (Box 333)
      - North Campus (Box 333)
      - Ombudsman (Box 333)
      - Orientation (Box 333)
      - Parking (Box 333)
      - Peer Institutions (Box 333)
      - Personnel (Box 333)
      - Plant Extension (Box 333)
      - Police (University of Michigan) (Box 333)
      - Police Oversight Committee (Box 333)
      - Politically Correct (Box 333)
      - Presidential Initiatives Fund (PIF) (Box 333)
      - President's Advisory Group on Minority Affairs (PACMA) (Box 333)
      - President's Advisory Committee on Women's Issues (PACWI) (Box 333)
      - President's Advisory Group (K-12 Education) (Box 334)
      - Presidents' Council of the State Universities of Michigan (Box 334)
      - President's Office (Box 334)
      - Professorships (Box 334)
      - Promotions (Box 334)